/==========\
|Problem 14|
\==========/

The following iterative sequence is defined for the set of positive integers:

n → n/2 (n is even)
n → 3n + 1 (n is odd)

Using the rule above and starting with 13, we generate the following sequence:

13 → 40 → 20 → 10 → 5 → 16 → 8 → 4 → 2 → 1
It can be seen that this sequence (starting at 13 and finishing at 1) contains 10 terms. Although it has not been proved yet (Collatz Problem), it is thought that all starting numbers finish at 1.

Which starting number, under one million, produces the longest chain?

NOTE: Once the chain starts the terms are allowed to go above one million.

/===========\
|Explanation|
\===========/

The program can be easily finished through a formulaic method.
However, time can be saved if any number is happened upon twice.
In this instance, it is verified that the number further along the chain cannot possess the longest chain.

We can use a recursive function as well as a map to keep track of all numbers.

The number with the most chains is 837799.